http://www.allthingsid.com/policies/privacy-policy

Bulk Lanyards | Badge Reels | ID Holders In Stock - We make Custom Face Mask Lanyards - Order Online Or Call 1-800-560-8158
Badge Holders
Popular
Clear Horizontal | VerticalProximity CardArmbandZipper ClosureName Tag HoldersColor
Custom PrintedColor BackColor ConferenceColor FrameColor TopHard Plastic
Open FaceEnclosedLuggage TagsBadge WalletsMagneticShieldedNo MinimumSpecialtyID Clips
Strap ClipsPins | Bulldog ClipsBadge Reels
Blank
Carabiner ReelRound ReelsSquare ReelsKey Bak ReelsBaumgarten ReelsPrinted
Custom Badge ReelsHeavy DutyRetractable LanyardsBadge Buddies
Design A Custom Lanyard
It's easy and fast to create a custom lanyard online. Design Now
ID Cards
Proximity
HID®Proximity Cards and RightProx™ CompatiblesIndala CardsAllegion | XceedIDOnline Id Cards
ID Cards Low Volume ID Cards Mid - High Volume Photography Backdrops
Custom Photo BackdropsGreen Screen BackdropsMotorized Photo BackdropsPhoto Stand BackdropRetractable Photo BackdropStanding Retractable BackdropShredders
Printer Ribbon ShredderHigh Security ShreddersNSA Approved ShreddersIndustrial ShreddersHole Punches
Id Slot PunchesCustom Hole PunchesLoyalty CardsBadge Racks and CasesName Tags
MetallicPlasticVisitor
Custom Printed PVC Visitor IdTempbadge One Step Visitor IdTempbadge Visitor Log BooksTempbadge Expiring Time SpotTempbadge Visitor Management SystemLaminating
Laminating PouchesLaminatorsPhoto CuttersCameras
CamerasTripodsID Printers
Datacard
Datacard Id PrintersDatacard Printer RibbonsDatacard CleaningDatacard Print HeadsIDP
IDP Id PrintersIDP Printer RibbonsIDP CleaningEvolis
Evolis Id PrintersEvolis Printer RibbonsEvolis CleaningPolaroid | Valid
Polaroid Valid Id PrintersPolaroid Valid Id Printer RibbonsFargo / HID
Fargo Id PrintersFargo Id Printer RibbonsID SoftwareBlank PVC CardsProximity CardsParking Permits
Parking Permit Hang TagsParking Bumper DecalsParking Window DecalsStatic Cling Parking PermitParking Violation StickersID Solutions
Healthcare ID SolutionsEducation ID SolutionsGovernment ID SolutionsEvent Passes and HoldersBarcodes
Barcode PrintersBarcode Scanners
Privacy policy
At AllThingsId.com, your privacy is our priority. We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you become a member is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. Our site uses a 128 bit encrypted SSL to increase the security of our customers information. However, we All Things Identification do not guarantee complete security on stored information.How Do We Use the Information We Collect?When you become an AllThingsId.com member, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and e-mail address as well as some demographic information such as gender.Your name and address information is used solely to process orders unless your prior consent is given. Without your consent, this information will NEVER be sold, given, rented or traded to others for purposes other than order fulfillment.Your demographic informationwill be used for several security purposes, to ensure you are who you say you are and in fact you are paying with your credit cards and not someone using your stolen credit cards.Our Use of Log FilesWhen you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.Site SecurityAll AllThingsId.com employees take your personal information very seriously. All employees must learn and obey our security policies. Access to member personal information is limited to key personnel. The information is ID and password protected.Links To Other SitesThis Web site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving the AllThingsId.com site and entering another Web site. These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.Legal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web siteSupplementationWe may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make sure that our members receive the order and to lower costs associated with our programs.Our Use of CookiesCookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter. The ability to select samples on our site is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in aggregate form. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, our site will not identify you when you enter and you will need to manually type in your ID and password.If you have any questions about our privacy policy please call us at 1-800-560-8158
Fast Fair Shipping
Same Day Shipping Before 12 EST No Hidden Costs
Price Match Guarantee
Our Value Can't Be Beat "Guaranteed"
ID Solution Consult
Let Us Help Find The Right ID Product For You
Purchase Orders Accepted
Government, Education, Healthcare, Corporate
